{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "email": "victor.souza@email.com",
      "password": "1234",
      "name": "Victor Souza",
      "profilePicture": null
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "email": "alexandre.souza@email.com",
      "password": "1234",
      "name": "Alexandre Souza",
      "profilePicture": null
    },
    {
      "name": "Anakin Skywalker",
      "email": "anakin.skywalker@starwars.com",
      "password": "darthvader",
      "id": 3,
      "profilePicture": null
    },
    {
      "name": "Obi -Wan Kenobi",
      "email": "obi.kenobi@hellothere.com",
      "password": "hellothere",
      "profilePicure": null,
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "candidates": [
    {
      "name": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
      "interview": "Scrum Master",
      "score": "90",
      "date": "2021-04-22",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Luke Skywalker",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor React Pl",
      "score": "75",
      "date": "2021-04-22",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Sheev Palpatine",
      "interview": "Scrum Master",
      "score": 600,
      "date": "2021-04-22",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "R2-D2",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor Java Jr",
      "score": 3500,
      "date": "2021-04-22",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "BB-8",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor Java Jr",
      "score": "92",
      "date": "2021-04-29",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "Han Solo",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor React Pl",
      "score": 2500,
      "date": "2021-05-10",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "Biggs Darklighter",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor React Pl",
      "score": "",
      "date": "2021-05-14",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "Ahsoka Tano",
      "interview": "Scrum Master",
      "score": "",
      "date": "2021-05-14",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "Padme Amidala",
      "interview": "Desenvolvedor Java Jr",
      "score": "",
      "date": "2021-05-16",
      "id": 9
    }
  ],
  "interviews": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "category": "Front End",
      "vacancy": "Desenvolvedor Angular Pl",
      "questionnaire": "Questionario Front End 3",
      "questionnaireId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "category": "Front End",
      "vacancy": "Desenvolvedor React Pl",
      "questionnaire": "Questionário Front End 3",
      "questionnaireId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "category": "Back End",
      "vacancy": "Desenvolvedor Java Jr",
      "questionnaire": "Questionário Back End 2",
      "questionnaireId": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "category": "Agile",
      "vacancy": "Scrum Master",
      "questionnaire": "Questionário Agile 3",
      "questionnaireId": "3"
    }
  ],
  "questionnaires": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Questionário Front End 3",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "category": "Front End"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Questionário Back End 2",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "category": "Back End"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "title": "Questionário Agile 3",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "category": "Agile"
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "pergunta FE 1",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 1",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "pergunta FE 2",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 2",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "pergunta FE 3",
      "difficulty": "fácil",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "pergunta FE 4",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 4",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "pergunta FE 5",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 5",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "pergunta FE 6",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 6",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "pergunta FE 7",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 7",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "pergunta FE 8",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 8",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "pergunta FE 9",
      "difficulty": "médio",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "pergunta FE 10",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "resposta esperada FE 10",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "pergunta BE 1",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 1",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "pergunta BE 2",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 2",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "pergunta BE 3",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 3",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "pergunta BE 4",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 4",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "pergunta BE 5",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 5",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "pergunta BE 6",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 6",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "pergunta BE 7",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 7",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "pergunta BE 8",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 8",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "pergunta BE 9",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 9",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "pergunta BE 10",
      "questionnaireId": 2,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 10",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "pergunta AM 1",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada BE 1",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "pergunta AM 2",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 2",
      "difficulty": "fácil"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "pergunta AM 3",
      "difficulty": "fácil",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "pergunta AM 4",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 4",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "pergunta AM 5",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 5",
      "difficulty": "médio"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "pergunta AM 6",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 6",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "pergunta AM 7",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 7",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "pergunta AM 8",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 8",
      "difficulty": "difícil"
    },
    {
      "question": "pergunta AM 11",
      "difficulty": "médio",
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 11",
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "pergunta AM 9",
      "difficulty": "médio",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "pergunta AM 10",
      "difficulty": "médio",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "pergunta FE 11",
      "difficulty": "médio",
      "questionnaireId": 1,
      "answer": "pergunta esperada FE 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "pergunta AM 11",
      "difficulty": "difícil",
      "questionnaireId": 3,
      "answer": "resposta esperada AM 11"
    }
  ]
}